[Music]
So looking
policy last class
and
let's convert from so
people relative important sample something like
expected value
[Music]
off
right so expected value of f x r x is
sampled according to p can be given by
expected value of f a * p a b q a
v a sample
from okay basic important sampling and sum
expression for so ch was
actually not some approximation here so these
approximates were also root
another sampler which
[Music] was
okay so
this is the
weighted importance sampling
estimator weighted importance sampling and
normalize so different price call
okay so yes I'm going to use in longing so people are talking about right x x x
r and what if f x x x in m o
[Music]
setting
start
actual
text
these
captivity
return n  Okay, not
pass, but more, let's
rate the probability of every given time I'm following
policy, let's rate the
probability of the given time I'm following the ...
Probability is starting to win an okay answer is
fine okay
[music]
x
so compute p x q
I need the piece rate I need piece I don't know the
p came and I don't what piece rate
live I you think about it we need p I only have a
ratio with q so I never need to
compute p and q separately l a need to
compute the ratio so take the ratio what happens is to
ratio right this product of ratios fine
son historically you for both products is
well as policy
so please
text ir so na I don to fi ratio p x ba
x so what did this b so if you think about it it's
tricky I should
approach l apo o w an on
left hand side a ya a running rebel sorry okay so what we have here so what is this correct
to what is important suppl r corre
to  Expected value a right so what is that value
function right so the value
function
of some state rate pa of a sum a rate all we have is
v
pi of a e equal to so
put the superscript in brackets it
denotes that this quantity comes from the ha
trait o this is 1 to a means I am running
a different trait so I put the
superscript not that there is a coming from the a
trait and the return is computed
starting
from
state okay so like wise I mean I need to have a the
[music]
ya
fine so yes ha a date colo
policy
ll okay or
policy pli
to explore more state I'm
following the policy pli so I can get a larger
sample of state
and
b policy then what I have is a part
of ri I want to do this as I have to read
the textbook r some nether a
big
pi the
int rate you l  No what I missed so just
fill it in
so there are a few tricks that they do in the
book they take this and convert this into an
incremental method where you can keep you don't have to wait until
you finish running the tractor
to compute this importance wait you can keep
updating it as you go along right and then
you can keep updating this estimate also as you go along
in the tractor you don't have to remember everything they give
you some small
tricks to make it incremental so an easy of
you to look it up if you are going to ever
implement this method this way you will do it not like this so but it really tries
to get you to read the
book right so some aran
sagar gi him to reading the book
anyway so fi fural so yd fur
control rful fur
control o ha change change fur
first with a it will it
change we need action  Value So what is
the problem with using action values ​​Any
specific problem you see with using action
values ​​Okay so I'm going to let you
actually go read the book Okay I'm not going to tell
you just go read the book and figure out how do
you do some of the policy control Okay
[appreciation]